<resources>
    <string name="mass_label">Mass:</string>
    <string name="mass_unit_kg">kg</string>
    <string name="mass_unit_lb">lb</string>
    <string name="count_bmi">Count BMI</string>
    <string name="empty_value">0.00</string>
    <string name="input_is_empty">Please provide value.</string>
    <string name="height_is_too_low">The value is too low. Make sure the data is in the correct units.</string>
    <string name="height_is_too_high">The value is too high. Make sure the data is in the correct units.</string>
    <string name="mass_is_too_low">The value is too low. Make sure the data is in the correct units.</string>
    <string name="mass_is_too_high">Value is too high. Please make sure that you used correct units.</string>
    <string name="height_label">Height:</string>
    <string name="height_units_cm">cm</string>
    <string name="height_units_in">in</string>
    <string name="app_name">BMI Calculator</string>
    <string name="change_units">Change units</string>
    <string name="success">Success</string>
    <string name="pending">Pending</string>
    <string name="underweight">Underweight</string>
    <string name="optimum">Optimum</string>
    <string name="overweight">Overweight</string>
    <string name="obesity">Obesity</string>
    <string name="describeUnderweight">You may not be eating enough or an underlying illness could be
        preventing you from gaining weight. Underweight adults are at increased risk of weakened immune system,
        fragile bones and may experience low energy levels. If you struggle to gain weight, see a GP.</string>
    <string name="describeOptimum">
        Adults in the normal range are considered to have a healthy weight. Maintain it with regular exercise and a healthy diet.
    </string>
    <string name="describeOverweight">A high proportion of adults fall into the overweight category.
        There are factors that may cause your BMI to be inaccurate - if you have high muscle bulk for example.
        That is why it is important to look at a range of measurements to get a better overall picture of your health.
        However, this is a good time to make an honest assessment of your lifestyle to see if you should
        reduce calories in your diet or increase the calories you burn with exercise. The higher you fall within this b
        racket the higher your risk of cardiovascular disease.</string>
    <string name="describeObesity">Being obese significantly increases your risk of developing heart
        disease and type 2 diabetes. If you fall into this category you should see a GP and ask their advice on bringing down your weight.</string>
</resources>